hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨， Spring 粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装Spring 提示
installment we're gonna talk about a big
分期付款，我们将谈论一个大
big exciting new feature that we just
我们刚刚推出的令人兴奋的新功能
announced at last week's epic spring i/o
在上周的史诗般的 Spring I / O上宣布
conference in Barcelona Spain this
会议在西班牙巴塞罗那举行
feature is really to stay safe or
确实可以确保安全或
Malaysian of support that's already been
马来西亚人的支持已经
there in some form or another across a
以某种形式存在于另一种
number of different projects that is to
要进行的不同项目的数量
say reactive transactions so we have two
说被动交易，所以我们有两个
interesting projects that support
支持的有趣项目
transactions at the moment in the
目前的交易
reactive space we have MongoDB which as
反应空间，我们有MongoDB作为
of 4.0 now supports transactions across
的4.0版本现在支持跨
discreet documents and we have our two
谨慎的文件，我们有两个
DB C which is a reactive spi and a
DB C是反应式SPI和
number of different implementations
不同的实现数量
based on that spi for talking to sequel
根据那个spi与续集说话
data stores and both these are reactive
数据存储，这两个都是反应性的
from the ground up they support
他们从头开始支持
asynchronous IO from the ground up and
从头开始的异步IO
they offer support for transaction so
他们提供交易支持，因此
here is an opportunity for an
这是一个机会
abstraction so while there is already
抽象，所以虽然已经有
individual support in MongoDB and I'm in
我在MongoDB中提供个人支持
the spring that a MongoDB project and in
一个MongoDB项目的 Spring
in the RT DBC projects for transactions
在RT DBC项目中进行交易
that are there is there has not been
那里那里还没有
some sort of sort of common standardized
某种常见的标准化
integration for both of them just like
两者的整合就像
there is right now for Springs platform
现在有Springs平台
transaction manager hierarchy so we're
事务管理器层次结构，所以我们
going to talk about is that new support
要谈论的是新的支持
we're going to look at it in both
我们将在两者中进行研究
MongoDB and in RT BC with a trivial
MongoDB和RT BC无关紧要
example which I of course I'll build
我当然会建立的例子
here and start Douglas bringing that ILO
在这里开始道格拉斯带来国际劳工组织
so I'm gonna go ahead and build a new
所以我要继续建立一个新的
application I'm gonna call this rx TX
应用程序，我将其称为rx TX
will use reactive MongoDB we use Lombok
将使用反应式MongoDB，而我们使用Lombok
we're gonna use the let's just use a
我们将使用让我们只使用一个
reactive web I'll actually just get rid
反应式网页实际上我会摆脱
of that later but we'll keep that there
以后，但我们会保留在那里
and I think that's probably all that we
我想那可能就是我们所要做的
need for now I'll bring in to that to
现在需要，我会介绍给
that om3 of spring boots open this
spring boot 的om3打开
downloads you ale or x TX dot zip
下载ale或x TX dot zip
this will spin up and of course first
这将旋转，当然首先
thing we're gonna do we're gonna we're
我们要去做的事情
gonna use MongoDB first we'll do this in
首先要使用MongoDB，我们将在
MongoDB terms first and I have MongoDB
首先是MongoDB条款，我有MongoDB
running on my local machine now keep in
现在在我的本地计算机上运行
mind you can't just use regular like if
介意你不能只使用常规的
you just did you install one going to be
你刚安装了一个
the resulting installation wouldn't work
结果安装将无法正常工作
in the reason is because you have to
原因是因为您必须
have a replica set and so I have this
有一个副本集，所以我有这个
goofy script that I use it maybe you
我用的愚蠢的脚本，也许你
might want to use as well just to get a
可能还想使用以获取一个
local replica set going so there's that
本地副本集进行，所以有
script right so it's just I'm creating a
脚本正确，所以我正在创建一个
data directory make the data directory
数据目录创建数据目录
and then among would do MongoDB replica
然后其中将做MongoDB复制
set equal to my replica set DB path data
设置等于我的副本集数据库路径数据
blah blah blah
等等等等等等
background that and then I evaluate
然后我评估的背景
replica said that initiate to to
副本表示发起到
initiate the replica set so so that's
初始化副本集，以便
that's the stuff I have to do to get a
这就是我要做的事情
MongoDB instance that works in a way
以某种方式工作的MongoDB实例
that I can use transactions right just
我可以直接使用交易
as I understand it MongoDB for that -
据我所知MongoDB为此-
should have distributed transactions
应该有分布式交易
okay you know multiple nodes but for now
好吧，您知道多个节点，但是现在
this is a I think it I think it's
这是我想的，我认为是
limited to one node I meant or at least
限于我的意思是至少一个节点
to one replicas said I'm not quite sure
一个复制品说我不太确定
how that works exactly but I know you
究竟如何运作，但我知道你
need a replica set so we have this and
需要一个副本集，所以我们有这个
now you can use our application here and
现在您可以在这里使用我们的应用程序了
I'm gonna do the normal things here I'll
我要在这里做正常的事情
create am let's see I think I want the
创建是让我们看看我想我想要
font be a little larger don't we so make
字体要大一点，不是吗
the font font okay here we go
字体好吧，我们去
and we want those to be let's say 24
我们希望那些可以说24
good and we're gonna create an object to
好，我们将创建一个对象
write data to the database obviously so
显然将数据写入数据库
clasp customer and we'll have a private
扣住客户，我们将有一个私人
string ID private string email alright
字符串ID私人字符串电子邮件
email works and then it'll be a document
电子邮件有效，然后它将成为文档
of course will have a primary key that
当然会有一个主键
will document a little map using the add
将使用添加文件记录一点地图
ID annotations
ID注解
data at all args constructor
所有args构造函数中的数据
norc's constructor right so just the
北欧的构造函数，所以
normal stuff and I'm gonna create a
正常的东西，我要创建一个
repository to persist and manage
存储库以持久化和管理
instances of this entity of course using
该实体的实例当然使用
the reactive credit repository managing
无功信用库管理
entities the type of customer was the
实体客户的类型是
primary keys of type of string uh and
字符串uh和类型的主键
then funny I want to UM use this so I'm
然后很有趣，我想使用UM，所以我
gonna create a test right but in order
会创建一个测试权限，但是顺序
for this to work I need a few things in
为了这个工作，我需要一些东西
order to in order to benefit from
为了从中受益
Springs transaction support so the basis
Springs交易支持如此基础
transaction operator here in order for
交易运营商在这里为了
this to work I need to create a few
要工作，我需要创建一些
things here
这里的事情
so transactional operator create passing
因此交易操作员会创建传递
in a reactive traps and transaction
在反应陷阱和交易中
manager and the transaction manager
经理和交易经理
implementation of course varies from one
实施过程当然有所不同
persistence technology to another so
持久性技术到另一个如此
we're gonna use a Mongo transaction
我们将使用Mongo交易
manager okay so let's say new Mongo
经理好，让我们说新的Mongo
transaction here best way to do it
交易这里最好的方法
reactive Mongo transaction manager and
反应性Mongo交易经理和
that's an implementation of this common
这是这种常见的实现
type called reactive transaction manager
类型称为被动交易管理器
it in turn expects a reactive Mongo
反过来，它期待一个反应性的蒙哥
database Factory so reactive Mongo
数据库工厂如此反应Mongo
database factory already and then DBF
数据库工厂已经存在，然后是DBF
get stuff so there's that now that
得到东西，所以现在有
should be enough for now let's go to our
现在应该足够了
test code and actually we'll just try
测试代码，实际上我们将尝试
this out we're gonna create a a when I
出来的时候，我要创造一个
created a service right to handle this
创建了处理此问题的服务权
transactional logic so we've got a
事务逻辑，所以我们有一个
repository a repository is good for a
存储库对
boilerplate sort of you know crud style
样样你知道克鲁德风格
stuff create read update delete you know
东西创建阅读更新删除你知道
the boring lifecycle management of data
无聊的数据生命周期管理
okay very simple stuff
好吧，很简单的东西
now we're gonna create a customer
现在我们要创建一个客户
service and we're gonna have a method
服务，我们将有一种方法
here that returns saved customers and
在这里返回保存的客户，
it's gonna write in bulk
要大量写
based on their emails okay so very
根据他们的电子邮件，很好
simple thing and I'm gonna implement
简单的事情，我要实现
this as a em as a thing that requires
作为一个em，这是一个需要的东西
multiple writes now there are better
现在多次写入有更好的
ways to do this but I want to have
做到这一点的方法，但我想拥有
multiple independent discrete writes so
多个独立的离散写入，因此
what I'll do is I'll say let's create a
我要做的是，让我们创建一个
publisher out of the name of the emails
电子邮件名称之外的发布者
rather I'm going to take each email and
而是我要接受每封电子邮件，
turn it into a new customer okay I'm
把它变成新客户好吧，我是
gonna take each one of those customers
要带走这些顾客中的每一个
and write it to the data means in order
并按顺序将其写入数据
to do that of course I need to inject my
为此，我当然需要注入我的
repository here so customer repository
这里的客户资料库
and we'll make this a service well.tell
我们将使其成为一项服务。
Lombok to synthesize a constructor so
龙目岛合成一个构造函数，所以
it'll just you know create a constructor
就知道创建一个构造函数
and for any field that's final little
对于最后一点的任何领域
kata a parameter and some storage for
kata一个参数和一些存储
that so let me do that and then customer
那让我先做然后再做客户
post right at save customer alright now
立即在“保存客户”中发布
there's our whole pipeline so there's my
有我们的整个管道，所以有我的
data and now what I'm gonna do is I'm
数据，现在我要做的就是
going to use we're gonna get three
要使用，我们将得到三个
different layers three different
三层不同
approaches to transaction management
交易管理方法
okay so the first one will be the I
好吧，第一个是我
think the most flexible so this dot well
认为最灵活，所以这个点很好
we need a transactional operator so
我们需要一个交易运营商，所以
private transactional operator all right
私人交易运营商可以
and this is sort of like the transaction
这有点像交易
template right you can you can just
模板的权利，你可以就可以
provide a new transaction callback right
提供新的交易回调权限
and you provide a publisher that's
而您提供的发布商是
returning something in the transaction
在交易中退还东西
and in this case I can just return this
在这种情况下，我可以退货
right remember we're not executing
正确的记住我们没有执行
anything yet right we're not actually
任何正确的事，我们实际上不是
executing that we've created a cold
执行我们制造了感冒
pipeline right a cold stream of data
流水线处理冷数据流
there's no actual data flowing through
没有实际的数据流过
this and so even though we defined the
即使我们定义了
transaction outside of the or they or
或以外的交易或
rather we define define the logic that
而是我们定义定义的逻辑
has transaction you know semantics we
有交易，您知道语义，我们
define that outside of the transaction
在交易之外定义
block it doesn't matter because we're
阻止无关紧要，因为我们
not executing it it only gave you only
不执行它只会给你
get to subscribe to in in the context of
在以下情况下订阅
the transaction and of course this is a
交易，当然这是一个
well-suited for lambda so that's very
非常适合lambda，所以这非常
simple
简单
and we turn that okay and this is this
然后我们就可以了，这就是这个
transaction template it's nice because
交易模板很好，因为
you can actually you know it is just
你实际上可以知道那只是
returning the exact same thing that we
返回与我们完全相同的东西
gave it it's returning us a publisher of
给它返回我们的出版商
customer so I could then compose that
客户，然后我可以撰写
with other streams I could continue
与其他流，我可以继续
processing it but only the stuff inside
处理它，但只处理里面的东西
of that transaction operator that
该交易运营商的
executes block would be executed inside
executes块将在内部执行
in the in the body of a transaction so
在交易主体中
now we've got this let's create a simple
现在我们有了这个，让我们创建一个简单的
test simple to test to test things out
测试简单，测试出结果
here okay and this will be a public
好的，这将是一个公众
class at run with spring render dot
与Spring一起运行的类渲染点
class spring loop test and we're just
类Spring 循环测试，我们只是
gonna create a test script basically
基本上会创建一个测试脚本
okay so test public void save all okay
好的，所以测试一下public void保存一切吧
throws
抛出
there we go and we're gonna inject our
我们去了，我们要注入我们的
transactional operator all righty
交易操作员没事
and actually no we're gonna inject our
实际上，我们不会注入
customer service here we'll say customer
这里的客户服务我们会说客户
service
服务
and all I'm gonna do is I'm gonna write
我要做的就是写
some data to the database now I didn't
现在我没有一些数据到数据库
actually define what will fail so this
实际定义什么会失败，所以这
is a this is a happy path kind of thing
这是一条幸福的道路
I'm not doing any validation on this
我没有对此进行任何验证
let's say that I go through each
假设我经历了每个
customer in the put in the publisher and
发行人中的客户
I decide that oh well you know one of
我决定哦，你知道吗
these has an invalid email
这些邮件无效
well I can't persist that so I'm gonna
好吧，我不能坚持下去，所以我要
do a do one next I'm gonna say okay
再做一件事我要说好
we're gonna assert that the customer get
我们要断言顾客得到了
an email dot contains and write if it
电子邮件点包含并写是否
doesn't contain that then it'll throw an
不包含它，那么它将抛出一个
exception and the transaction operator
异常和事务运算符
will see that it and then we'll roll
会看到它，然后我们将滚动
back the transaction it'll emit an error
退回交易将发出错误
basically and then a rollback the
基本上然后回滚
transaction so the email must contain
交易，因此电子邮件中必须包含
okay there's our updated code so now I'm
好的，有我们的更新代码，所以现在
gonna test that script Adam what I'm
要测试那个脚本亚当我是什么
gonna do is I'm gonna write some data to
我要做的是写一些数据到
the database I'm gonna say well first of
首先我要说的数据库
all gonna delete everything in the
全部都会删除其中的所有内容
database so we'll say create this dot
数据库，所以我们说创建这个点
customer service dot or sorry needs that
客户服务点或对不起需要
repository to do that so what I'm doing
仓库来做到这一点，所以我在做什么
is I'm using the reactive the reactor
我正在使用反应堆吗
step verifier of course to to make short
步骤验证器当然要简短
work of running this test that has
运行该测试的工作
reactive dependencies here something
反应性依赖这里的东西
customer pause drive delete all and then
客户暂停驱动器全部删除，然后
I'll expect it to be complete right I
我希望它是完整的我
think that works so let's try this
认为可行，让我们尝试一下
that should work so I'm resetting the
应该可以，所以我要重置
database there should be nothing in the
数据库中应该没有任何内容
database at this point
此时的数据库
okay good now let's write some more data
好吧，现在让我们写一些数据
so when you say this deck customer posit
所以当你说这副牌客户
or a dot went to the insert don't really
或在插入点上有一个点不是真的
want to say this dot customer service
想说点这个客服
dot save all will be eight at a comm be
点保存全部将是八点
at Viacom C at C calm and d @d calm so
在Viacom C，C冷静，d @d冷静，所以
we're expecting there to be four records
我们预计会有四项记录
in the database now so expect next count
现在在数据库中，所以期待下一次计数
will be four and we should have four
将是四个，我们应该有四个
results from the same operation there
相同操作的结果
those are all valid emails great what
这些都是有效的电子邮件
about let's do a query to find
关于我们进行查询以查找
everything the Navy is to confirm as
海军要确认的一切
much so I'll say dot create this to
所以我会说点创建这个
customer service that's fine as our debt
客户服务就像我们的债务一样好
repository that find all expect next
找到所有期望的存储库
count will be equal to four okay there's
计数将等于四个好吧
that and then finally let's write two
然后最后让我们写两个
bad records to the database and confirm
不良记录到数据库并确认
that after we've written that that it's
在我们写完之后
gonna take so we should see it roll back
要采取，所以我们应该看到它回滚
and so we should see that the total
所以我们应该看到总数
number of records in the database is
数据库中的记录数为
still four okay
还是四个还好
so let's try that again dot save all you
因此，让我们再次尝试点保存所有
know one and to expect error dot verify
知道一个并期望错误点验证
so we're expecting that this should
所以我们期望这应该
result in an error and we're expecting
导致错误，我们期待
that neither record even not the first
既没有记录也没有第一
one at the second one will have been
第二个是一个
written so here
这样写在这里
well actually we can try one
好吧，我们可以尝试一个
you know what try eight at me calm they
你知道什么尝试八对我平息他们
go so that it's a or better yet ii at be
去吧，这是一个或更好的ii
calm okay so we should see one of them
冷静好吧，所以我们应该看到其中之一
not written so we should see that
没有写，所以我们应该看到
they're both rolled back even though one
他们都回滚，即使一个
is valid okay because it was an
是有效的，因为这是一个
exception so now we're gonna say this
例外，所以现在我们要说这个
dot customer service dot sorry
点客户服务点对不起
repository that find all dot expect next
找到所有点的存储库期待下一个
count here and that should be equal to
在这里计数，应该等于
four stop okay so let's see what happens
四站好，让我们看看会发生什么
if we run this
如果我们运行这个
okay what are we doing wrong
好吧，我们在做什么错
Oh
哦
right expect next count one sure but
正确的期待下一个肯定
again
再次
okay so we can see that even though we
好吧，即使我们
got two records back we've got one
有两张唱片，我们有一张
regular record in one error that when we
定期记录一个错误，当我们
did a query of the database we only had
对我们只有的数据库进行了查询
four records in the native a stone and
四记录在当地人的石头和
that's that's to say that these two were
那就是说这两个是
rolled back there they they were in the
回滚他们在那里
same transaction the same logical
相同的交易相同的逻辑
transaction and so we can see that we're
交易，所以我们可以看到我们
using the transactional operator to do
使用事务运算符来做
that right into to enclose all of this
包含所有这些权利
logic in one logical transaction now
现在在一个逻辑事务中进行逻辑
this is one way to use transactions in
这是在
spring it is very low-level but it's
Spring 是非常低级的，但是
nice because you can give it any
很好，因为你可以给它任何
publisher and it'll close that publisher
发布者，它将关闭该发布者
in a transaction it's like I said it's
在交易中，就像我说的那样
very akin to the transaction template
非常类似于交易模板
and Spring Framework and this of course
和Spring Framework ，这当然
does live in Spring Framework you can
确实存在于Spring Framework中，您可以
see this is actually part of spring
看到这实际上是 Spring 的一部分
frameworks transaction support it's
框架交易支持
under the PAC package reactive okay so
在PAC包装下反应还好吧
that's one way to do it the other way to
这是另一种方式
do it is actually to say that we're
真的是说我们
going to do this as this that
要这样做
transactional operator dot transaction
交易算子点交易
like that and so you just return
这样，所以你就回来
customer flex okay so here we're we're
客户可以，所以我们在这里
actually using the transaction operator
实际使用事务运算符
again but we're actually adding it to
再次，但我们实际上是将其添加到
the end of an existing pipeline rather
现有管道的末端而不是
than wrapping it the effect should be
比包装它的效果应该是
the same let's run our test and see what
同样，让我们​​运行测试，看看有什么
happens
发生
okay there's our test good that works
好吧，我们的测试产品行得通
just fine
正好
and now the other way we can do this is
现在我们可以做到的另一种方法是
we can use declarative transaction
我们可以使用声明式交易
management okay it's a way that way that
管理好，这是一种
works is you say Antony will transact
作品是你说安东尼会交易
your management and here just like in
您的管理，就像在
spring just like in regular synchronous
Spring 就像定期同步
blocking transactions you can just say
您只能说阻止交易
add transactional and just return that
添加事务性并返回
so we don't need this anymore all right
所以我们不再需要这个了
yeah not bad huh so the three different
是的，还不错吧，这三个不同
ways to use the transaction management
使用交易管理的方式
support here we've done this for MongoDB
支持这里我们已经为MongoDB完成了
now let's try RTD BC okay so with our
现在让我们尝试RTD BC
TBC not a lot it has to change obviously
TBC并没有很多，它必须明显改变
you know they're not the same kind of
你知道他们不是同一种
dated datastore when the document
资料储存库过时的文件
database one's a sequel data store so
数据库是一个续集数据存储
I'm going to use post quiz I'm going to
我将使用测验
turn this object into a thing that has a
把这个物体变成具有
monotonically incrementing primary key
单调递增主键
get really document annotation I'll go
得到真正的文档注释，我去
back to my build here I'm gonna replace
回到我的构建，我要替换
some of the dependencies namely the moma
一些依赖关系，即妈妈
to be support with the equivalent and
得到同等的支持
new support for for transaction
新的交易支持
management so get rid of that and we
管理，所以摆脱它，我们
want a new experimental dependency so I
想要一个新的实验依赖性，所以我
need to actually this is not actually
需要实际上这不是实际上
part of the spring boot or spring data
spring boot 或Spring 数据的一部分
release chains and so I need to bring in
释放链，所以我需要带进去
this custom thing here dependency
这个自定义的东西在这里依赖
management dependencies
管理依赖
dependency spring boot dependencies are
依赖Spring Boot的依赖是
GBC and this is 0.1 dot o 2 m 1 and
GBC，这是0.1点o 2 m 1和
it'll be a type palm scope input all
这将是一个掌上型输入全部
right so there's that and with that in
对，所以有那个
place we can now bring in the equipment
现在我们可以携带设备的地方
the appropriate dependencies for our TBC
TBC的适当依赖项
itself this including this new
本身包括这个新的
experimental but you know very
实验性的，但你非常了解
interesting and very promising auto
有趣且很有前途的汽车
configuration for our TBC all right this
我们TBC的配置好了
is new as well it's a spring boot
也是新的，它是 spring boot
started that yes okay bring that in and
开始，是的，把它带进去，
that turn we can also bring in this
这样我们也可以带来
spring boot starter for just our TVC
我们的TVC的 spring boot 启动器
without spring data so if you don't want
没有 Spring 的数据，所以如果你不想
the repository support then you don't
存储库支持，那么您就不需要
need you don't need to bring it in you
需要你不需要把它带进你
can just bring in the DBC you know the
可以带进DBC，您知道
database client and and stuff like that
数据库客户端和类似的东西
but okay either way this is both these
但是，无论如何，这都是这些
are both here everybody's post-credits
都是每个人的贷方额度
not MongoDB so I've got post quiz okay
不是MongoDB，所以我已经发布测验了
so no we want the orchid UVC driver
所以不，我们要兰花UVC驱动程序
don't we so that would be I owe our to
我们不是吗，那是我欠我们的
BC
公元前
okay
好的
and we want to catch you pull support
我们想抓住您的支持
all right good stuff now let's see what
好东西，现在让我们看看
else has to change well I think I think
否则我必须改变得很好
it'll work
会的
actually I think that's pretty much it
其实我觉得差不多
well I miss him
好吧，我想他
I got to change this of course so this
我当然要改变这个
is the arc TBC transaction manager and
是弧形TBC交易经理，并且
it expects a pointer to the connection
它需要一个指向连接的指针
factory and the connection factory of
工厂和连接工厂
course is the thing that we use to
当然是我们习惯的事情
describe our connection to the database
描述我们与数据库的连接
article database and we're going to be
文章数据库，我们将成为
using a any connection factory here
在这里使用任何连接工厂
Postgres connection back three and in
Postgres连接返回三和中
order to get that connection factory
为了获得那个连接工厂
I'll inject the URL using the property
我将使用属性注入URL
placeholder we'll come back to that in a
占位符，我们将在
second so spring that are - you see that
第二个 Spring 是-你看到
URL connection in factories dot get URL
工厂中的URL连接dot获取URL
all right so there's that and now of
好的，所以现在
course we need the property itself or
当然我们需要财产本身或
can figure that now equals and then that
可以算出现在等于然后
is the JDBC URL for my database like
是我的数据库的JDBC URL，例如
give me a second
你稍等一会儿
all right this is our to DC it's the new
好吧，这是我们的DC，这是新的
protocol prefix : PostgreSQL : for such
协议前缀：PostgreSQL：用于此类
four slash orders at localhost
在本地主机的四个斜杠命令
five four three two website orders okay
五四三二网站订单还可以
so that's my little my database running
所以这就是我的数据库正在运行
my local machine here let's try that
我的本地机器在这里尝试
same test again
再次相同的测试
cool so there's the same test again
很酷，所以又有相同的测试
written again with a new code and you
再次用新代码编写，您
can see that we were able to you know
可以看到我们能够知道
get the same results right we saw the
得到相同的结果，我们看到了
same behavior orders orders select all
相同行为的订单订单全选
from customer there's that right we saw
从客户那里，我们看到的是正确的
four records I'd have to go here to
我必须去这里的四个记录
MongoDB it'll be DB that customer gotta
MongoDB客户必将成为DB
find there's our full record all right
发现这里有我们的完整记录
in my friends I hope you got something
在我的朋友们，我希望你能得到一些东西
out of this I hope you'll give out the
因此，我希望你能给出
new give give the new transaction
新给予新交易
support a try
支持尝试
obviously there's a lot of interesting
显然有很多有趣的事情
opportunities here with more and more
这里的机会越来越多
databases coming online as being
数据库进入在线状态
supported and having a reactive
支持和反应
intubations this support I think means
插管，我认为这意味着支持
that now a whole class of preloads that
现在，整个类的预加载
we thought sort of unattainable
我们认为这是无法实现的
unobtainable in the reactive world are
在反应世界中无法获得的是
now available so that's exciting
现在可用，令人兴奋
thanks so much for watching and as
非常感谢您的收看和
always we'll see you next time
总是我们下次见
you
您